<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>https://docs.technotim.live/</id><title>Techno Tim Documentation</title><subtitle>Documentation for Techno Tim YouTube videos for all your copy pasta needs!</subtitle> <updated>2022-04-12T13:13:11-05:00</updated> <author> <name>Techno Tim</name> <uri>https://docs.technotim.live/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://docs.technotim.live/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="https://docs.technotim.live/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2022 Techno Tim </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Fully Automated K3S etcd High Availability Install</title><link href="https://docs.technotim.live/posts/k3s-etcd-ansible/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fully Automated K3S etcd High Availability Install" /><published>2022-03-26T10:00:00-05:00</published> <updated>2022-04-04T21:43:52-05:00</updated> <id>https://docs.technotim.live/posts/k3s-etcd-ansible/</id> <content src="https://docs.technotim.live/posts/k3s-etcd-ansible/" /> <author> <name>Techno Tim</name> </author> <category term="kubernetes" /> <category term="k3s" /> <summary> Setting up k3s is hard. That’s why we made it easy. Today we’ll set up a High Availability K3s cluster using etcd, MetalLB, kube-vip, and Ansible. We’ll automate the entire process giving you an easy, repeatable way to create a k3s cluster that you can run in a few minutes. A HUGE THANKS to our sponsor, Micro Center! New Customers Exclusive – Get a Free 240gb SSD at Micro Center: https:/... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Perfect Proxmox Template with Cloud Image and Cloud Init</title><link href="https://docs.technotim.live/posts/cloud-init-cloud-image/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Perfect Proxmox Template with Cloud Image and Cloud Init" /><published>2022-03-19T10:00:00-05:00</published> <updated>2022-03-26T09:58:30-05:00</updated> <id>https://docs.technotim.live/posts/cloud-init-cloud-image/</id> <content src="https://docs.technotim.live/posts/cloud-init-cloud-image/" /> <author> <name>Techno Tim</name> </author> <category term="proxmox" /> <summary> Using Cloud Images and Cloud Init with Proxmox is easy, fast, efficient, and fun! Cloud Images are small images that are certified cloud ready that have Cloud Init preinstalled and ready to accept a Cloud Config. Cloud Images and Cloud Init also work with Proxmox and if you combine the two you have a perfect, small, efficient, optimized clone template to provision machines with your ssh key... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>A Hypervisor Built on Kubernetes - Cloud Native HCI with Harvester</title><link href="https://docs.technotim.live/posts/meet-harvester/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Hypervisor Built on Kubernetes - Cloud Native HCI with Harvester" /><published>2022-03-12T07:00:00-06:00</published> <updated>2022-03-13T15:28:49-05:00</updated> <id>https://docs.technotim.live/posts/meet-harvester/</id> <content src="https://docs.technotim.live/posts/meet-harvester/" /> <author> <name>Techno Tim</name> </author> <category term="kubernetes" /> <category term="rancher" /> <summary> Rancher released a next generation open source HCI software hypervisor built on Kubernetes that helps you run virtual machines. With Harvester you can create Linux, Windows, or any virtual machine that can be easily scaled and cluster giving your high availability virtual machines with a few clicks. It also gives you a platform to automatically create HA RKE1, RKE2, and K3S Kubernetes clust... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>TrueNAS Scale Apps - Official, Unofficial, Docker, and Kubernetes</title><link href="https://docs.technotim.live/posts/truenas-scale-apps/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TrueNAS Scale Apps - Official, Unofficial, Docker, and Kubernetes" /><published>2022-03-02T07:00:00-06:00</published> <updated>2022-03-13T15:28:49-05:00</updated> <id>https://docs.technotim.live/posts/truenas-scale-apps/</id> <content src="https://docs.technotim.live/posts/truenas-scale-apps/" /> <author> <name>Techno Tim</name> </author> <category term="truenas" /> <summary> TrueNAS SCALE is here and with it comes new way of installing and managing applications. You can install official apps, unofficial and community apps using TrueCharts, and also any Docker image or Kubernetes deployment with helm. Join me as we dive into managing applications and exploring TrueNAS SCALES’s new app engine that runs Docker, Kubernetes, and K3S. Watch Video If you’re looking ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Building your first Dockerfile, Image, and Container</title><link href="https://docs.technotim.live/posts/custom-docker-image/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Building your first Dockerfile, Image, and Container" /><published>2022-02-26T07:00:00-06:00</published> <updated>2022-03-13T15:28:49-05:00</updated> <id>https://docs.technotim.live/posts/custom-docker-image/</id> <content src="https://docs.technotim.live/posts/custom-docker-image/" /> <author> <name>Techno Tim</name> </author> <category term="homelab" /> <summary> We spin up all types of containers on my channel in my tutorials, but we have yet to build our own custom Docker container image. Today we’ll start from scratch with an empty Dockerfile and create, build, and run our very own custom Docker image! We’ll learn all the commands that everyone should know when building and maintaining images with Docker. This tutorial is a great way to get star... </summary> </entry> </feed>
